Hello
hello friends welcome to Strokes friends
very good news has come from Stree Attack
firstly it has declared its quarter final
result date and at the same time the
company has
also announced the deferral for its shareholders but the
best news is that it has declared the record date of deferral
so let's quickly
see when its quarter final
result is going to come and also let's
see what is the record date of deferral
etc so friends we have come on
that notice of the company in which the company had issued
a notice here you will see
first the board meeting of the company is on 20th April
and on 21st the board meeting of the company is on 15th April i.e. the
Q4 results of the company here I
adjust a little bit yes see here one
that the result of HCL Tech Water for is
going to come you can see it clearly here
now look here the company has
also announced the diverging date for its shareholders
so this is very good news for their shareholders
but and most importantly
here  It is written, see, 29th April
is the record date for Diff. That is, the
accident happened on 28th April. So if you
want Diff. then you will have to
buy the shares of this hair pack within 27th April, only then you will get the
division, that is, only then you will be
eligible for Diff. So friends, very
good news is being seen for the war with SC-ST
and here it has also been
learned that those who want to make a new entry
for Diff. they will have to
enter within 27th April. But
still I would like to say one thing here,
entry is not done in any stock just for Diff.
If you have a long term
perspective and you like the business model of the company,
then after this the fundamentals
also have to be checked. Entry
in any stock is done only after these three conditions are fulfilled properly. So
friends, that's all for now. If
you liked this information, then
definitely subscribe to the channel
because on this channel we keep
bringing updates related to the stock market.
So we will meet in the next video, till then
Goodbye to